

Phan Huu Dinh Web Developer

Email: phanhuudinh@hotmail.com

Mobile: 0905221193

Address: 02 Cam Nam 9, Hoa Xuan, Da Nang

Day of birth: 22/11/1993

Summary

I have almost 2 years of web programming experience as a fullstack .NET developer with strong knowledge at both frontend backend. With more than 1 year as a game programmer, that very helpful for me to power up my skills about code performance and creation mindset.

Work Experience

Fullstack Developer at IOT Link

November 2016 - Present

Web development bold client and server side. Design and implement module for awesome project (*Xinkcity*)

Research and apply new technique for new version of *Xinkcity* by SPA architecture use ReactJs for frontend and Asp.Net for backend.

Development web modules, web api for mobile app and support teamate.

Deployment and config environment for web server.

.Net Developer at NAL Solution

August 2016 - November 2016

Development windows and web application for Japan outsource project by C#

2D/3D Game programmer at Gameloft

June 2015 - August 2016

Java 2D game creation, implement game actor follow design, optimize performance for best quality, support graphic-designer to use optimize tools. Complet first creation project (NOVA ORIGIN) in my studio (DAD) with my teamate.

C++/JAVA 3D Game publishing, implement anti hack/cheat for game, scale for multy devices.

Key	Skil	Is
-----	------	----

C# Javascript ReactJs HTML/CSS SQL MVC Web Api Git Scrum

Other Skills

React Native VueJs SVN C/C++ Java NopCommerce Dotnetnuke Unity Game development

Education

Hue University of Science

Grade: Good

Major: Information Technology